Okay, so hello everyone now as we have already done with this cloudinary.js setup now
we are let's go to the order controller.js and complete the complete this update profile
a pay so usually we are going to take the try and catch block okay so try block and then
in catch we are going to catch there are so catch and then error and now inside the try block
what will you do the first thing which we are going to do is to take the profile pick so profile
pick profile pick equal to request dot body so from the request we are going to take the profile
and now let's take the user ID so user ID equal to request dot a user dot underscore ID now what
we are going to do we are going to check if this profile pick so if this profile pick doesn't exist
so profile pick we are going to take and then we are going to return a status return res dot
status and then we are going to return a response of 400 dot chase and that the message would be
profile profile pick is required okay control and save now suppose if
the pick is present then in that case what we are going to do so in that case we are going to
take up the profile pick okay so const suppose upload image equals to await
so we are going to take from clouding a result of it cloudinary dot upload a dot upload and
profile pick profile pick and we are going to update the user okay so const updated user
so await so user dot find by we are going to take a method find by and update so we are going
to update the profile pick of the person okay so in that case what we are going to do is we are
going to take the user ID okay and after that for the profile pick part we are going to
just make new object and in this new object we are going to use the uploaded image so upload
image then secure URL and we are going to just take one another object suppose if there's a new
one so new equals to true and now we are going to return the status like suppose if we are
successfully able to upload the profile picture so in that case RES dot status 200 dot
JSON we are going to return the updated user okay similarly whatever we have done in the case
of the cache we are going to cache there so we are going to return the status of 500
and dot JSON we are going to return a message if we are not able to upload the profile picture
like error in updating profile okay so error in updating the profile and comma the error would be
error dot message okay so we have done with this update profile thing so in the next video
we are going to do something else okay